Stanislav Dubuk

Web developer

stanislavdubuk@gmail.com +7 (978) 147-66-59

Front End Developer with two years of professional experience working with React.js, JavaScript (TS), HTML and CSS (SCSS). My passion for development combined with Business Management education and experience helped me to create great tech solutions as well as to contribute to business development and customer satisfaction.

Key Skills

- React.js (Redux, Redux Toolkit, MobX, Next.js)
- JavaScript / TypeSctipt
- HTML / CSS (SASS, SCSS)
- REST API and back end integration
- · Docker, Webpack
- Adobe Photoshop, Figma
- Scrum

Professional Experience

Front End Developer

Edstein | January 2021 - Present

- Responsible for contributing to development and engineering of a Learning Management System web application for corporations
- Created multiple completely new features such as Calendar Module with monthly events, Chats Sidebar using WebSockets, Appraisal Module including reports with charts and many more
- Participated in each step of the product development process from concept to development improvement for features reaching more than 200,000 users across all clients
- Mentored an intern that became part of the front end team after three months
- Implemented new development practices such as including extra es-lint settings, creating code styles
 guides, getting rid of development branch and stages in favour of Docker and separate branches for QA
 team, Webpack configuration and implementation of new libraries
- Participated in code review and training sessions for newer developers
- Worked with a scrum software including 40+ members

Department Supervisor

The Home Depot | February 2019 - August 2020

- Managed day-to-day operations in hardware department
- Supervised, trained, coached and developed associates in the department to ensure customers receive
 excellent service and can easily find the merchandise they need
- Provided an input to the associates on the appraisal of their performances
- Maintained the records of the department and generated routine and ad-hoc reports for management as requested
- · Kept track of inventory in the department by ordering new supplies as needed

Office Administrator

Mount Carmel Medical Center | September 2018 - February 2019

- · Supervised administrative staff and divided responsibilities to ensure performance
- Managed agendas/travel arrangements/appointments etc. for doctors
- Assisted medical staff whenever necessary
- Managed advertising and marketing strategy
- Managed database of the patients and followed up about appointments

Customer Service Representative

Campus Living Centres | July 2017 - February 2019

- Produced assigned front office reports and tasks
- Handled reservations, check-ins, check-outs, and account settlement in a professional manner
- Communicated pertinent information between staff
- Handled phone calls with patience and decorum
- Assisted students and guests during their stay or visit
- Communicated with a team of supporting staff

Education

College diploma in Business Management and Entrepreneurship Algonquin College at Ottawa, Canada | January 2016 - June 2017

Bachelor's degree in Management

Tavrida National University at Kyiv, Ukraine | September 2012 - January 2016